Nighttime and Idol
Now, and the third
Music
More and more at ease.
Very good. It's better that way.
Really?
I was a bit nervous at first.
Yes, at first.
Now, the third element that makes Tate-san...
Music.
Yes, music.
What is it? What kind of music?
I listen to all kinds of music.
But I can't listen to Western music.
I can't understand what they say.
I'm a lyrics person, basically.
I have to know what the lyrics mean.
If I don't know the lyrics
Well, it's kind of nice.
Is it nice?
It's nice.
Thank you very much.
There's a part of me that's like, "Oh, no, I don't need the lyrics.
Because it's got a totally cool vibe.
It's not like that.
Ah...
The melody alone isn't enough.
There are songs that I like just for the melody
But the lyrics are more important, basically.
Oh, that's because I can sympathize and
I sympathize with them.
I like to listen to songs that match my current feelings.
I wonder... I wonder...
Yes, I sympathize with the lyrics.
Well, let's see, now, the lyrics I like the most...
The lyrics that fit me the best.
It depends on the time of the year, doesn't it?
It's totally different.
Yes, it is.
And the phrases...
Well, can you tell us which song?
Well, I'd like people who are working hard in life to listen to this song.
It's called "Jellyfish".
Yes, it's very good.
It's really good.
It has really good lyrics.
I especially like the chorus.
I don't remember the lyrics.
Heh.
I don't know...
The melody is there, but the lyrics aren't.
Wow, it was all unexpected.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
That's amazing.
The lyrics don't come out at all.
Oh, so, so...
It's a song from our group.
When we're trying to cheer people up or something.
Oh.
This song is like...
It's a good song when we want to encourage people.
I know.
What's that?
Dada?
Kaiwat Avatar.
So you still listen to a lot of music?
Yes! I listen to a lot of music! I listen to music all the time!
When you're on the road?
When I'm on the move, or as soon as I wake up in the morning.
Wow.
Music is such an indispensable element of your life.
Yes!
Yes! Mr. Date's three elements are money, meat, and white rice.
Music!
Yes!
Start!
Thank you very much!
I know I've said a lot, but I'm surprised how often we have conversations without any substance.
You're being watched.
Oh, am I being shown?
Am I being shown?
No, I'm not.
This show is...
Mr. Ghost.
Mr. Rikabo.
Mr. Sudo
Mr. Ghost
Mr. Manuru Neko of Kouku-ku
Sent to you courtesy of Miyu-chan
Thank you all!
Thank you